{
    "data": {
        "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "whining",
                "answer": "нытье"
            },
            {
                "question": "seize",
                "answer": "воспользоваться"
            },
            {
                "question": "opaque",
                "answer": "непрозрачный"
            },
            {
                "question": "restrictions",
                "answer": "ограничения"
            },
            {
                "question": "tradeoff",
                "answer": "компромисс"
            },
            {
                "question": "indent",
                "answer": "отступ"
            },
            {
                "question": "encounter",
                "answer": "столкновение"
            },
            {
                "question": "convention",
                "answer": "условность"
            },
            {
                "question": "comprised",
                "answer": "состоит"
            },
            {
                "question": "to tie",
                "answer": "связать"
            },
            {
                "question": "purged",
                "answer": "продували"
            },
            {
                "question": "recap",
                "answer": "резюмировать"
            },
            {
                "question": "bench",
                "answer": "скамейка"
            },
            {
                "question": "parcel",
                "answer": "пакет"
            },
            {
                "question": "bulb",
                "answer": "колба"
            },
            {
                "question": "reward",
                "answer": "награда"
            },
            {
                "question": "diamond",
                "answer": "бриллиант"
            },
            {
                "question": "sweep",
                "answer": "подметать"
            },
            {
                "question": "enjoy",
                "answer": "наслаждаться"
            },
            {
                "question": "fix",
                "answer": "фиксировать"
            },
            {
                "question": "midwife",
                "answer": "акушерка"
            },
            {
                "question": "milkmaid",
                "answer": "доярка"
            },
            {
                "question": "notary public",
                "answer": "государственный нотариус"
            },
            {
                "question": "pharmaceutist",
                "answer": "фармацевт"
            },
            {
                "question": "conciliation",
                "answer": "соглашательство"
            },
            {
                "question": "ado",
                "answer": "суматоха"
            },
            {
                "question": "vice versa",
                "answer": "наоборот"
            },
            {
                "question": "concurrent",
                "answer": "параллельный"
            },
            {
                "question": "Defer",
                "answer": "Перенести"
            },
            {
                "question": "caveat",
                "answer": "предостережение"
            },
            {
                "question": "invasive",
                "answer": "агрессивный"
            },
            {
                "question": "kudos",
                "answer": "почет"
            },
            {
                "question": "sanitized",
                "answer": "дезинфицировать"
            },
            {
                "question": "suspend",
                "answer": "приостановить"
            },
            {
                "question": "clumsy",
                "answer": "топорный"
            },
            {
                "question": "verbose",
                "answer": "подробный"
            },
            {
                "question": "generic",
                "answer": "общий"
            },
            {
                "question": "expose",
                "answer": "разоблачать"
            },
            {
                "question": "named after",
                "answer": "названный в честь"
            },
            {
                "question": "expose",
                "answer": "разоблачать"
            },
            {
                "question": "namely",
                "answer": "а именно"
            },
            {
                "question": "propagate",
                "answer": "размножать"
            },
            {
                "question": "desperate",
                "answer": "отчаянный"
            },
            {
                "question": "inflate",
                "answer": "раздувать"
            },
            {
                "question": "objective",
                "answer": "задача"
            },
            {
                "question": "merely",
                "answer": "просто"
            },
            {
                "question": "redundant",
                "answer": "избыточный"
            },
            {
                "question": "whirl",
                "answer": "завихрение"
            },
            {
                "question": "obstacle",
                "answer": "препятствие"
            },
            {
                "question": "toughest",
                "answer": "жестким"
            },
            {
                "question": "affair",
                "answer": "дело"
            },
            {
                "question": "twist",
                "answer": "твист"
            },
            {
                "question": "pregnant pause",
                "answer": "значительная пауза"
            },
            {
                "question": "tenacity",
                "answer": "цепкость"
            },
            {
                "question": "rebound",
                "answer": "отскок"
            },
            {
                "question": "controversial",
                "answer": "спорный"
            },
            {
                "question": "conducted",
                "answer": "проведены"
            },
            {
                "question": "anecdote",
                "answer": "история"
            },
            {
                "question": "stance",
                "answer": "позиция"
            },
            {
                "question": "compromise",
                "answer": "компромисс"
            },
            {
                "question": "succinctly",
                "answer": "сжато"
            },
            {
                "question": "disparaging",
                "answer": "пренебрежительный"
            },
            {
                "question": "vocalize",
                "answer": "вокализировать"
            },
            {
                "question": "overlooked",
                "answer": "упускать из виду"
            },
            {
                "question": "pinpoint",
                "answer": "определить"
            },
            {
                "question": "ad hoc",
                "answer": "для этого случая"
            },
            {
                "question": "tedious",
                "answer": "утомительный"
            }
        ]
    }
}